(Penny:)and two bags came out.
(Raj:)I bought the first one,
(Raj:)it didn't fall.
(Bernadette:)Here.
She's here, the baby's here!
- Oh! Oh.
- Congratulations!
(Amy:)How's Bernadette?
(Howard:)Tired, but great.
(Howard:)They're both great.
(Penny:)Does the baby have a name yet?
(Howard:)We have named her Halley.
- Oh!
- Oh, like Halley's comet.
(Howard:)Exactly.
(Howard:)Also like the comet,
Bernadette said
(Howard:)she's not gonna have sex
with me for another 75 years.
(Amy:)That's not a real thing,
he's just joking.
(Howard:)I'm gonna get back.
(Howard:)Thank you for staying up,
I can't wait for Halley to meet
(Howard:)her new aunts and uncles
(Howard:)and godfather.
(Raj:)Really?
(Penny:)Of course.
You hear that, Stuart?!
(Raj:)I've got a dog and a godchild,
you have nothing!
Oh, look at all the babies!